Guide to the National Student Christian Federation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Administrative/Governance Committees, Series III
  - Budget and Finance Committee
    - Account book and correspondence re. expenses, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Budget reports, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Contribution receipts, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence between Herluf Jensen nad Otto Bremer includes budget reports and meeting minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Expenditure reports, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Expenditure reports, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Meeting minutes, 1961-1966 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Report on Budget and Finance matters to the III General Assembly of the NSCF, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Summary of income and expenditures, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Budget proposals, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Budget reports and statements of income and expenditures, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Comparison budget, member movement and agency undesignated contributions, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Contribution receipts, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Contribution receipts, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence re. appointments to the Budget Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Expenditure reports, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Interseminary budget history, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Letters re. NSCF contributions from member movements and agencies, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Letters welcoming new members of Budget Committee, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Proposed 1963 budget, notes about NSCF budgets, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Working file of William Lovell, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Budget reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Budget reports, proposed budget, summary of NSCF WSCF contributions, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Invoices and receipts, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - WSCF receipts, January-February 1964 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - WCSF receipts, March 1964 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - WSCF receipts, April 1964 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - WSCF receipts, March-June 1964 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - WSCF receipts, August-Septmeber 1964 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - WSCF receipts, October-November 1964 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - WSCF receipts, December 1964 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Memos and reports, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Central Committee
    Records consist of memos and documents sent to Central Committee members, and meeting minutes. The Central Committee acted for the General Assembly during the interim between the assemblies. The members of the committee where elected during the General Assembly. The committee usually met once a year, and much of the program direction was directed through this committee. Note to the researcher: when studying the Central Committee's minutes follow up with the Executive Committee minutes. The Executive Committee picked up the Central Committee's work in its interim.
    - Correspondence re. meeting attendance includes rosters, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Directory, 1960-1961, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Development Consultation, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Memos, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Memos, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Memo drafts, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Minutes, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Open Letter from the Central Committee. Includes Articles of Operation for the UCM, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Position papers re. Task and Direction of NSCF, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Progress report, miscellaneous papers, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Statements on the right to dissent, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Working file of M.O. Williams, 1961-1965 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Working file of M.O. Williams, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Executive Committee
    The Executive Committee conducted the work of the General Assembly and Central Committee in their interims. It is where the various commissions and committees of the NSCF met to discuss program planning.
    - Correspondence, Van Voorhis, Richard and Zabriskie, Phillip, 1960, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Directory, List of NSCF events, and Meeting agendas, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Memos, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Reports and proposals presented to Executive Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Working paper: Some Thoughts About the National Student Christian Federation as Community and as an Organization by Herluf Jensen, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Inter-movement Council
    Records consist of memos, minutes, and documents shared at meetings. The Inter-Movement Council was created to give the students in NSCF more involvement within the organization. The Council primarily addressed student concerns such as the Civil Rights movement, Nuclear Disarmament, and peace concerns. It was made up of two student delegates from each movement with the NSCF President chairing the council.
    - Memos, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Minutes, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Papers, proposals, and reports including "The Student Movement: NOW" by Gayle Graham Yates and "The New Mood on Campus" by Art Brandenberg, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Personnel Committee
    Records in this subseries consist of correspondence related to searches for NSCF positions, memos, and meeting minutes.
    - Correspondence re. search for a General Secretary, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Correspondence re. search for a General Secretary, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Correspondence re. search for a General Secretary, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Correspondence re. search for a General Secretary, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Correspondence re. search for CWAIS Director, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Correspondence of William Lovell as Acting General Secretary, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - Correspondence re. search for General Secretary, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - Correspondence, General, 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Correspondence re. search for CWM Leadership, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - Job descriptions includes correspondence of M.O. Williams, 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - Memos re. search for a General Secretary, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - Task of the General Secretary and Assistant General Secretary, undated (Box 12, Folder 131)
- Commission on World Mission, Series IV
  This series is divided into five subseries: Administrative and General Records, Field Program Committee, Financial Appeals and Contributions, Literature and Study Committee, and Speaking Engagements of C. Alton Robertson. All are arranged alphabetically by subject except the last subseries which is organized chronologically. Within the Field Program are three subseries: Committee Records, Field Staff, and International Travel Associates. The Field Staff and International Travel Associates subseries are arranged alphabetically by last night of traveling staff.
  - Administrative and General Records
    Records in this subseries relate to the overall programming of the Commission on World Mission. These materials are primarily memos, minutes, and reports.
    - Annual report, 1959-1963 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Annual report, 1963-1966 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Budget and Finance Committee, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Budget and Finance Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Commission meeting minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Commission meeting minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Fall 1962 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Spring 1963 (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Fall 1963 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Spring 1964 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Fall 1964 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Spring 1965 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Fall 1965 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Commission meeting minutes, Spring 1966 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Concerns: Angola, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Concerns: Brazil Coup d'etat, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Concerns: China, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Concerns: Latin America, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - Concerns: United States of America's occupation of the Dominican Republic, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Consultative Committee on Enlistment of the Commission on World Mission, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - Correspondence re. the Campus Ministry Association Conference, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - Correspondence of M.O. Williams, 1960-1966 (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 155)
    - Executive Committee: Correspondence, minutes, and reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - Executive Committee: Correspondence, minutes, and reports, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 157)
    - Executive Committee: Correspondence, minutes, reports, and joint meeting with the CWAIS, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 158)
    - Executive Committee file of M.O. Williams includes memos, minutes, and notes, 1960-1966 (Box 15, Folder 159)
    - Farewell dinner for C. Alton Robertson materials, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 160)
    - Fellowship of Student Volunteers includes Declaration card, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 161)
    - Finances, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - Invitations to Fellowship of Student Volunteers Executive Committee, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - Life and Mission of the Church program emphasis, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - Memos, 1961-1963, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - Minutes from Consultative Committee on Education and Consultative Committee on Enlistment for Missionary Vocation, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - New Patterns in Missions Committee, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - Nominating Committee: Correspondence re. appointments and rosters, 1962, 1965-67 (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - Nominating Committee: Correspondence, memos, minutes, nomination forms, and progress reports, 1960, 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - Notes of M.O. Williams, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 170)
    - Personnel Committee: Correspondence, minutes, and reports, 1962-1965 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Policy history, 1952-1960 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Position papers, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Position Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - Reports: Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - Report of the Sixth International Student Missionary Convention Sponsored by the Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 176)
    - Search for a new CWM Director, includes correspondence with Paul Schrading, August 1965-September 1965 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - Sermon given at the opening worship service of the Missions Today Seminar by Douglas Sloan, undated (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - Seminar on The Churches and International Affairs at the Center for United Nations., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - Special interim meeting and position papers subcommittee re. the direction of the Commission on World Mission, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 179a)
    - Staff manual, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Working file of M.O. Williams, January-May 1966 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - Young Friends Committee of North America information, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - Field Program Committee
    The Field Program Committee Records consist of annual reports, briefing conferences for new travel staff, correspondence, meeting minutes, and promotional materials for visiting travel staff. The Field Staff records consist of correspondence, itineraries, and reports from traveling staff, particularly staff promoting the 1964 Ecumenical Student Conference. The International Travel Associate records contains correspondence, itineraries, and reports from international field staff.
    - Committee Records
      - Annual reports, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 183)
      - Briefing Conference for Travel Staff, Spring 1961 (Box 17, Folder 184)
      - Briefing Conference for Travel Staff, Fall 1961 (Box 17, Folder 185)
      - Briefing Conference for Travel Staff, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 186)
      - Campus visits: Procedures and packet information, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 187)
      - Correspondence re. proposal for International Travel Associate program, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 188)
      - Correspondence re. search for Travel Staff personnel, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 189)
      - Correspondence, general, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 190)
      - Correspondence re. proposed Travel Staff, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 191)
      - Correspondence re. requests for International Travel Associate, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 192)
      - Correspondence, memos, and minutes, 1958-1963 (Box 18, Folder 193)
      - Correspondence, memos, and minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 194)
      - International Travel Associate program, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 195)
      - International Travel Associate Revision Committee, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 196)
      - List of conferences and field program visits, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 197)
      - List of Travel Staff, 1942-1960 (Box 18, Folder 198)
      - Meeting agendas and minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 199)
      - Meeting agendas and minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 200)
      - Promotional materials for the Weekend Conversation on Missions and International Ecumenical Team and the Chicago Summer '66 Project, 1961, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 201)
      - Summary of Frontiers Seminar by C. Alton Robertson, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 202)
      - Visits from Travel Staff organized by state and year, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - Field Staff
      - Abraham, Carl-Viljoen, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 204)
      - Bathgate, John, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 205)
      - Beers, Richard, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 206)
      - Brand, Paul, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 207)
      - Brown, William, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 208)
      - Caldwell, Lawrence, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 209)
      - Cochrane, Robert G., 1960 (Box 19, Folder 210)
      - Cook, Douglas, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 211)
      - Cuban-American Team: Jim Monsonis and Rudolfo Juarez includes photographs, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 212)
      - Deer, Donald, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 213)
      - Dorman, Ivan, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 214)
      - Downs, Ray includes photograph, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 215)
      - Fenske, Elizabeth includes photograph, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 216)
      - Gass, Eric, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 217)
      - Hollingsworth, Stanley includes photograph, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 218)
      - Juten, Shirley, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 219)
      - Kagawa, Ukemo includes photographs, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 220)
      - Kochs, Dennis, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 221)
      - Kokuma, Francis, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 222)
      - Lehtonen, Risto, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 223)
      - Long, Loy Li, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 224)
      - Nathaniel, Vilma, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 225)
      - Northrup, Robert, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 226)
      - Phillips, Carlisle includes photographs, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 227)
      - Poulard, Grady includes photograph, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 228)
      - Rollins, Metz, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 229)
      - Rosser, H. Edwin includes photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 230)
      - Schoch, Ruth, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 230a)
      - Schoder, Ronald, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 231)
      - Smith, R. Caldwell includes photograph, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 232)
      - Swanson, Rolla, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 233)
      - Warner, James includes photographs, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 234)
      - Whitcomb, William, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 235)
    - International Travel Associates
      - Barkat, Anwar, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 236)
      - Carino, Feliciano, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 237)
      - Chipenda, Jose, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 238)
      - Divas, Armando includes photograph, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 239)
      - Elango, Lovett, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 240)
      - Matsudo, Ichiro includes photograph, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 241)
      - Ntlabati, Gladstone (did not travel), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 242)
      - Opoku, Nathan, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - Financial Appeals and Contributions
    The Financial Appeals and Contributions subseries contains letters sent to Protestant denominational foreign and home mission boards requesting funding assistance. Also, includes receipts if payment was received.
    - Augustana Lutheran Church: Board of World Missions, 1955-1962 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1954-1962 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - American Baptist Home Mission, 1956-1960 (Box 21, Folder 246)
    - Church of Brethren: General Brotherhood Board, 1954-1958 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Churches of God in North America: Board of Missions, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Correspondence re. board appropriations, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Disciples of Christ: Board of World Missions, 1954-1961 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1955-1959 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Evangelical United Brethren Church: Board of Christian Education, 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Evangelical United Brethren Church:, 1955-1962 (Box 21, Folder 253)
      The Financial Appeals and Contributions subseries contains correspondence asking for financial assistance from Protestant denominational foreign and home mission boards.
    - Methodist Board of Missions: Joint Section of Education and Cultivation, 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Methodist Board of Missions: Women's Division of Christian Service, 1957-1961 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States: Board of Christian Extension, 1956-1960 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States: Board of Christian Education, 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States: Board of World Missions, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1957-1961 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Reformed Church in America: Board of Education, 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 260)
    - Reformed Church in America: Board of North American Missions, 1956-1962 (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - Reformed Church in America: Board of World Missions, 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 262)
    - Requests for board appropriations, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - United Church of Christ: Board of Christian Education, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - United Church of Christ: Board of Homeland Ministries, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - United Church of Christ: Board of International Missions, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - United Christian Missionary Society, 1957-1960 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - United Lutheran Church in America: Board of Higher Education, 1956-1962 (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - United Lutheran Church in America: United Lutheran Church Women, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1957-1962 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Foreign Missions, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of National Missions, 1955-1962 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Commission on Ecumenical Missions and Relations, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - Women's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Literature and Study Committee
    The Literature and Study Committee files contain annual reports, mailing lists, and meeting minutes. This subseries also contains drafts of publications published by the Commission on World Mission. The Careers in Mission series contain drafts and research material as the publication was updated for a reprint.
    - Address labels and membership list, 1958-1960 (Box 23, Folder 275)
    - The Agricultural Missionary: Correspondence, re. Revisions, drafts, and research materials, 1949-1963 (Box 23, Folder 276)
    - Annual reports, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 277)
    - Basic Books Reading Course on World Mission of the Church: Correspondence re. publication, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 278)
    - Basic Books Reading Course on World Mission of Church: Drafts and galley proofs, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 279)
    - Basic Books Reading Course on World Mission of the Church: Research materials, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - Called to be Sent: Correspondence, drafts, and galley proofs, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - Careers for Christians in Communications: Memos and sample copies, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - The Christian Doctor and The Missionary Task: Correspondence re. Publishing, draft, and research materials, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 283)
    - The Christian Doctor and the Missionary Task: Critiques, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 284)
    - The Christian Doctor and the Missionary Task: Research materials, 1950-1960 (Box 23, Folder 285)
    - Christian Horizons: Current openings, undated (Box 23, Folder 286)
    - The Christian Nurse and the Missionary Task: Correspondence re. publication, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 287)
    - The Christian Nurse and the Missionary Task: Drafts and galley proofs, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 288)
    - The Christian Nurse and the Missionary Task: Research materials, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 289)
    - The Christian Teacher and the Missionary Task: Correspondence re. publication., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 290)
    - The Christian Teacher and the Missionary Task: Drafts, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 291)
    - The Christian Teacher and the Missionary Task: Research materials, 1951-1957 (Box 24, Folder 292)
    - Correspondence, general, 1959-1966 (Box 24, Folder 293)
    - Correspondence re. Career Index newsletter and Career Series pamphlets, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 294)
    - Correspondence re. composition of pamphlet the Christian's Calling, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 295)
    - Creation of the Careers in Christian Missions pamphlets, 1949-1957 (Box 24, Folder 296)
    - Frontier Seminars promotional materials, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 297)
    - Jobs on Your Doorstep: Research materials, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 298)
    - Jobs at Your Doorstep: Revision drafts, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 299)
    - Meeting minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 300)
    - Meeting minutes, 1960-1961, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 301)
    - The Missionary Wife: Galley proof, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 302)
    - The Ordained Ministry and the Missionary Task: Correspondence re. critiques and publication information, 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 303)
    - The Ordained Ministry and the Missionary Task: Drafts, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 304)
    - The Ordained Ministry and the Missionary Task: Research materials, 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 305)
    - Prospectus for books on Latin America and Mission of the Church in North America, undated (Box 25, Folder 306)
    - Servants of God in People's China: Notes of M.O. Williams, undated (Box 25, Folder 307)
    - What is a Missionary by Douglas Webster: Correspondence re. publication, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - Working Abroad as a Christian: Correspondence, drafts, and galley proofs, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 309)
    - Working Abroad as a Christian: Research materials, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 310)
  - Speaking Engagements of C. Alton Robertson
    The Speaking Engagements of C. Alton Robertson consist of materials presented at various conferences and consultations in which Roberts was invited. Includes correspondence regarding conference arrangements, drafts of presentations, and conference materials.